shall we
pray Heavenly
Father we thank you once again this
evening we are here before
you it is in the Heat and climax of
fasting that we encounter a lot of
Trials a lot of
challenges a lot of
Temptations probably some of us have
succumbed and fallen into
sin against you alone have we sent
because you alone can sanctify you alone
can Purge you alone can cleanse now
creating us a new heart and renew a
steadfast Spirit within us may your
spirit never depart from us is our
prayer in Jesus holy name
amen our message tonight is
titled thank God for smaller
mercies thank God for smaller
mercies you meant
well and there's nothing wrong you have
done you didn't deserve what you're
going
through so far you've remained
faithful you've refused to give
up you convicted it's the right thing to
do it looks unreasonable in the eyes of
man and to the
world but God is saying keep moving
you're
tired you're weak you're
worn and all you want is to wake up one
fine morning and find the Lord AS stand
your night in
today that is everyone's
desire you can be so
lost in the ultimate
Victory and lose sight of the smaller
victories that should be cheering you up
along the
way and I know you want it so
badly until you miss to see the hand of
God in the process of
things a statement I love making
seeming Victory belongs with the devil
but ultimate Victory belongs with
God seeming Victory belongs with the
devil but ultimate Victory belongs with
God let me pray once again thank you
Lord breathe life into this
message let it speak to us according to
our
circumstances may we be encouraged lift
our spirits to keep fighting until we
have ultimate Victory because this is
our prayer in Jesus name
amen there's been a
drought for how many years in Elijah's
time three and a half there's been a
drought
find that story in the book Patriarchs
and
Prophets and you love the description
Ellen White
makes on how the land looked like during
the three and a half
years three and a half years is so long
to have a drought so
long and I
remember after the contest
on Mount
Camel elah had to kill the prophets of
ba is
it and uh in verse
41 First Kings chapter
18 then Elijah said to
Ahab go
up eat and drink for there is the sound
of abundance of rain
M it's been a long time experiencing
droughts now saying go up eat and drink
because me Elijah the prophet I've heard
the sound of abundance of what rain
there's rain
coming friends I know it's tough in
whatever you're going through but
there's a sound of abundance of
rain I know it's
tough so Ahab went up to eat and drink
and elah went up to the top of
camel then he bowed down on the ground
and put his face between his knees must
have done this is it like
this I don't know what he did was all
his knees on the ground what or he was I
don't know whatever it was but what I
know is that his face was
between his kn
and said to his
servant go up now look toward the sea so
he went up and looked and said there is
nothing and seven times he said go again
I like it
because he told his Serv go look toward
the sea and he went the first time and
he came back and said I have seen
nothing he said go
again and he went out again toward the
sea he
looked and he came back and reported
there was
nothing he said go
again the third time he went looked
toward the sea and he came back reported
I see nothing El
you let you say the fourth time go and
the man went when the man of God speaks
he speaks with sanity say go again the
fourth time and his servant went looked
toward the sea he didn't see anything
came back and said man of God there's
nothing fifth
time sixth time he came back he reported
I see
nothing then it came to pass the seven
time that he said when he came back the
seventh time he said H there's a
cloud as small as a man's hand rising
out of the sea so he said go up say to
Ahab prepare your chariot and go down
before the rain stops you so when he
went the seventh
time he came back and
reported I see a cloud Rising the size
of a man's
hand which man has the biggest hand
here must have been something like this
Rising this is very little he was to
face toward the what the sea
my question is was the was the did the
cloud rise the seventh time or it was
there from the first
time uhhuh what are you
thinking
huh was the cloud there the first time
or it was just Rising the seventh
time the cloud was there from the first
time
the problem
was the drought had ravaged the land so
badly that all they wanted was rain and
not a
cloud all they wanted was what rain the
they they wanted rain so badly that they
were not interested in the process of
how rain
comes just
drop I thought we check the clouds and
we say huh it's going to do what to rain
so he went the first time he didn't see
anything because in his mind he wants
rain and nothing else because he's had
Elijah tell Ahab that I hear the sound
of abundance of rain so what is eyes
have focused on is the real rain not how
the rain is processed and Elijah keeps
telling go back until you see it and
many times we are in tough situations
the Lord is processing your Victory you
are a able to see the small masses the
size of a man's hand all you're focused
on is the
rain
hey I pray that this daughter of God
will forgive me but the spirit tells me
to use experience I don't plan to share
people's stories they pop out in the
middle of a summer so I believe is
Spirit L I never plan
she calls me she
says I have been fasting my husband left
the
house a week
ago so I started
fasting and when I
fasted on day three is that what she
said I can't
remember but just pick what is important
in the
story she says she dreamed me Pastor
Mur delivering her and her
husband and then she woke up and in the
morning the husband called
her and asked her if she can send him
fair so that he
comes don't say am men too
first so she told the husband she's not
sending
so she's asking me Pastor he doesn't
work I F his life but he uses my
money to fund a lifestyle with
women so her parents have told her let
him learn his lesson I've not responded
to that she could be watching but
probably this could be her response if
you're not ready for God's answer don't
ask if you're not
ready for God's response for the prayer
you've made never
ask because if you were praying because
he
disappeared and you dream in the night
and in the morning he calls you send me
fair I come but your pride tells
you I find his life if I give him fair
to come he might go again and that keeps
hurting
her that is how the world reasons
you can only say that if it was not your
husband it was your
boyfriend but when it is your husband or
your child it doesn't matter how many
times you keep repeating the same thing
and you don't see a change because
you're bent hell bent to save
them how many times do we pay school
fees and our children don't do
exams how many times have you paid
school fees at the University and he
didn't
sit how many
how many parents have funded education
at the University and then they say oh
four years when are you graduating they
say graduation is coming in November and
then he disappears only to learn he
dropped out in year
two but you've been paying School
fee tell me who has disowned their
children because they've done that tell
me no one disowns their children but why
is it easy to Dishon a
husband I told you the other day he a
subject one day we'll find time discuss
given a choice between your son and your
husband pick your
husband yeah you're still
saying remind me you know on Sabbath
there's no on Sabbath there's no
material because 10 days end on Friday
so remind me we discussed that Sabbath
afternoon I've said it twice and you're
still
reluctant if you're not ready for the
blessing you have prayed for just don't
ask because if your husband disappears
and you pray and he calls and says sends
me fair I come so what were you praying
for
what were you praying
for the fact that he has called and
asked for fair to
come is a cloud the size of a man's hand
so he disappeared for months or
years and then he calls
you and he says I've sent you School fee
and then you realize he's only sent
school fees half School fee for one
child and you have five and then you
rant and
say what now why if you couldn't send
all the school fees so what was a point
of him sending that half School fee for
one child is a cloud the size of a man's
hand because sooner or
later it is going to
rain and at times the Lord is just
testing you to see if you're ready for
what you
asked at times we ask mixed with our
asks it's called asks our asks is mixed
with
pride such that you want the answer the
way you want it you you you want God to
respond the way you want you want to
Define to to Define how the response
comes I'm repeating if you're not ready
for what you asked for don't even
attempt to
ask and so there there are many things
God has done in our life despite the
hardships we are going through you can
sit clearly and say for for real I'm
suffering my husband has been away for
too long or this and this has been
happening but the truth is I am still
alive the truth is I was left with
children but they're still going to
school the truth is he left but I have
made progress in this and this manner
you you can actually count your what
Your Blessings while they were away that
is the TRU
but you see you're so focused on him
coming and at times they come after 6
years 7 years 5 years 3 years they come
and then they sit there in your house
for one month and you say oh god of
Heaven Jehovah you have answered my
prayer and that is your testimony for
the next four sabbaths and then Sabbath
four Sunday morning he
disappears then you begin to question
God did you really answer my prayer why
then did you have to bring him back if
you knew he was all going to stay the
Lord is showing you this is the cloud
the size of a man's hand that is that
it's like you have heard the sound of
abundance
ofering it is evidence there's rain
coming
I think there are many things we need to
ask God for
forgiveness he's come
through but we have murmured and
complained I know you will bring all the
thoughts that you have out there what if
he's coming to take advantage of me this
what we fight is a do or die we have no
ishish is
is and we depend on God for victory
if they had intentions of using us
taking advantage the Lord will turn it
to glorify his
name for every little Mercy you
see thank
God the lord loves to hear us giving him
thanks now if you can't thank him for
the little movie he has made will you
really thank him when he finally does it
I'm asking you will you be able to it's
just like saying if you cannot tithe 200
will you tithe 2
million if if tithing 200 is a struggle
just 20 Shillings will you tithe
200,000 because you can work out
clearly 200 tithe 20 20 is enough for
two Tomatoes will you will you tithe
200,000
cuz that's almost roofing for a
house let us learn to thank God for
smaller
mercies and your spiritual antenna
should be so up to notice that this is
actually God's hand this is not man's
hand this is God's
hand when when I was
doing the office here in
Nairobi is a move I made by
faith because I felt my services were
needed more out
here across the board not just
Adventists so the spirit impressed upon
me I had some
savings cuz I'm I'm trying to complete
my mama's house so I have some
savings that I was to use it to
complete but one time after prayer in
the morning it just flashed in my head
take those
savings set up a local presence in
Nairobi from that office you will get
your money back to complete you Mama's
house it's a move I made by
faith and even how I got the office I
didn't search the Holy Spirit led me
to I think it's only Abel who's been to
my
office I think it's only app it's a nice
office also didn't expect to get
it I also didn't
expect I our charges are just to keep
the mission doors office
open we don't charge for profit we
charge to keep the mission door
open and I remember I could only
afford because I was told I
do I do a deposit for two months and one
month rent then I said I'll do two
months and two months rent so that I'm
not managing I'm not doing crisis
management and the month I'm beginning
is when I'm trying to think where do I
get rent I didn't want that so I cleared
all my savings I did that those are now
four months is it two months deposit two
months rent and then I did um I fished
the office nicely it's a nice place
you'll come you'll visit it's a nice
nice place nice
place everyone who walks in says say
Pastor are you being a lure here or what
he say I still have my L instincts even
though I'm married in kissy I still have
my little bit
s and the rest of the monies I used to
fund other expenditures you know I'm
using my
savings and I told
God this money can't pay rent in
January and we've just open the
office so it's a new office that was in
November it's a new office I don't know
when it will generate money to even pay
one month's
rent that day it was my week one in the
office I visited with a friend of mine
week one in the
office and I was fasting that day I
think it was on her Wednesday and she
had
guests apparently a friend from the US
and I was traveling on Thursday
night so Thursday I came to the office
and I was going back to the house to
pick my stuff and go back to kissum so
that Thursday she called me and told me
my friend wants to see you before you go
says my I've not even shaken her hand
and the way everyone in the US know
Pastor M so I must shake her hand and
also go and say I met her so I got into
the house house I parked my stuff and
then I knelt down to pray before I took
supper and I told God I'm clearing the
first
week how these doors will be kept open
is solely in your hands I have no idea
and I have an office admin I must pay
there's no one you'll employ and tell
them business has not started making
money so bear with me no you
can't so I said how I'll pay my office
admin provided I keep the door open and
pay the office admin me you know how I
how I live because me I don't believe I
survive I don't survive in this world
when God dies then I'll begin to survive
but for as long as he still liveth no
child of God survives we live I say God
you know me how I live we've lived with
you for the last 17 years so I haven't
died
yet and then they come
in and we greet each other
and and she tells me you know what
Pastor I know I don't want to call names
I know so that that my friend I know
she's your friend but you'll be
surprised I'm more of a friend to you
than her and I said how he said me I
watch you on YouTube every other day so
where are you going to I said no I'm
catching a bus at 10:30 so why couldn't
you take a flight I said you know when
you when you start business you don't
begin with flight
how do you begin business with flights
say flights will come later on and he
said okay
um uh so I'm explaining why I can't take
a flight and I'm telling her you know
the savings I had I have paid rent I
have I have uh finished the office so I
don't think I have what I can use for
flights but I have what I can use for
for
bars and then she says okay then how
much is your
rent and I looked at her now you're
meeting someone for the first
time and I told
her I did two months deposit 2 months
rent a month's rent is 35,000 so I did
140 and then she told me I'm sorry I
know I'm Kenyan but as we live in the US
we have lost the language of Kenyan
shillings how much
I those so I worked out very fast
dollars I took a calculator
phone and she says allow me do your two
months rent January and
February and I told God I hear the sound
of abundance of
rain on my first week in the office
someone is already covered
January
February it is
a cloud the size of a man hand that
office will stay
open because rain is
coming I pray
you you'll be sensitive enough to know
this is God and as you
lament also thank him he says do not be
anxious for anything but by Prayer by
supplication and
Thanksgiving make your request known to
who he loves to hear us thanking
him thank him you didn't die I mean how
many women are in a mental facility for
marriage that didn't
work how many women how many men have
committed suicide for a marriage that
didn't
work but you're still
sin people will ask you ah you why is it
you don't have a sense of fashion you
know there's there's struggles we go
through when you hear someone comment
you look at them twice and say God
forgive her for she does not know what
she's
doing you're in a serious battle you
cannot even take notice of the fact that
you're losing weight people are telling
you you're losing weight but you just
can't notice because you fine I mean
you're so peaceful inside the outside is
being worn out but the inside the Lord
keeps renewing it every
day you're so strong
inside and by the way who goes to the
battlefield from the salon
who have you seen kdf soldiers women
with
makeup I I have a friend here who works
with kdf she's she's there she's a
military person I love that girl she
will tell
you they don't go to the battlefield
with
makeup because you're in the B they say
the only thing they apply are those
paint is it where is she she's somewhere
there the only thing they apply is what
is paint not
makeup but you you in deep trouble you
don't want to share with anyone you want
to cover it with makeup so that you look
good my in the battlefield there's no
time to even figure out there's a
manicure CU you're fighting the outside
looks so rugged but our spirit the Lord
renews every other
time we shall look good in due
season huh I used to weigh 48 at least
today I'm
63 my blood levels had gone down to
five today I have all the blood I
need and I look back and tell
God I would have been in madari but no I
am in Eden's
Spain I would have been dead but I'm
still
walking I would have been disoriented in
life but I am leaving my
purpose because your ministry is born
where you've been
broken and your testimony is found where
you have been
restored so the Lord doesn't just allow
us to be broken probably there's a
Ministry that he wants you to take care
of so let's learn to give thanks to God
for the little meres even though the
situation suggests otherwise we didn't
take chicken but there's something on
the
table I don't know how many times I took
porridge porridge white porridge with my
children because there was not enough
to to do ugali and we took porridge
without sugar I think for years my
children learned to do a drink without
sugar their taste buds got used
to and that is our
supper and there's a way I raised my
children that let's thank God for it was
the house that we would do worship then
take our uji and then sleep and we would
story and laugh our hearts out because
we knew God was in control I tell you
the next day when we get H we will cook
ugali but we will do skuma Wei that
doesn't have oil it only has salt for us
he that was a small Cloud the size of a
man's
hand I had every reason to complain
I didn't know God was squeezing
[Music]
me and today what came out of the
squeezing is a company that I
run a Ministry that I
ran and it's on that day I
sat I remember when I had my th thir
born these things make me a emotional
but today I've learned to be
strong I just come from
town I had my third born sakuro and when
I entered our bedroom I found him
sleeping on the
bed and I didn't have any
money he was on napkin you know napkin
not diapers napkin and wungu had not
burned the paper bags you remember the
paper bags are black black and I think
my mother had done a hole down there too
see the way paper bag is like this so I
done a hole here and a hole here so the
legs went in and then it was pulled up
and
tied and I think I
locked the
door and I
sobed I
cried and when I was done
I placed my hands on the boy and I said
it will never happen
again no one must provide for me no one
shall provide for me no one will provide
for me I am my own rescue me and God
there's nothing the two of us canot do
because life has to move forward
forward life has to move forward it
didn't stop me from having more kids
there are three kids after
Soo in fact those after Soo are
twins then after twins we have the last
one who's one year 6 months and I keep
telling my
husband if it comes no problem
I'm Not
Afraid today my children can eat what
they
want they can have what they
want and I made sure I made sure sure my
children don't get lost in the
circumstances I taught them to love
their father respect their father and
participate in his Rescue
Mission they love their father while
absent so you can imagine when he
came to
date they don't
I don't exist they see they father to
date because I knew
if if I don't ship that beit in their
life they'll be disoriented in life they
will grow with bitterness they will grow
with a lot of
hatred and I didn't want that for my
children I can tell you I look at my
children and I see greatness in all of
them and at times I tell God make them
like you made Philip's daughters they
were all prophetesses make my children
all preachers and I can see preaching in
all of them apart from hoe who does not
know to speak well but for the rest all
of them I see a gift of music coming up
I see a gift of preaching coming up for
all my
children oh
I was not even sure of our firstborn
even me I had my firstborn preaching the
first time she came to New Life I've
never seen her
preach but the teachers kept telling me
she would go to school and she'll tell
me I'm the one Speaking today at the
assembly and I wondered what is she
going to say but there's a teacher who
kept telling me you have a brilliant
girl so one time they took her
compositions and they thought they had
been
plagiarized because that level of of
English was not for a Kenyan high school
student so I said I asked her one day
can I have one of your books you've done
composition and I looked at it and said
God so when she preached around four
times so when I was supposed to be in
new life and I couldn't afford all the
days I sent her for the first two days
and I told Pastor K I'm sending you
someone and he said do I said my
daughter I've never heard her preach
you're sending someone you've never
heard preach you've just heard stories
from school that when she preaches
teachers teachers discuss her the whole
time in the stuff room so I said okay
let me let me just trust what I have
been told and send her I was listening
to her for the first time and I said
what so the other day we were in church
I was changing baby diapers in the
afternoon and kids classes had begun and
I had a child preaching teaching about
50 children ages 0 to around
10 with strength and vigor and when I
came out it was
so and I said yes he does devotions in
the house but he never does them the way
he's doing it here he was he was in
control he had the command you
know said
God I go back home from missions like
this and I found them singing and I I
had an alter I have never heard from
sakuro and I said can you guys sing
again and they said Mom tomorrow we are
singing in church this is the song I
always go find they have done songs so
I'm only taught the night to Sabbath and
then I also go stand there and and sing
but I can tell there's a gift of
music and I tell God it was not for
nothing that I went through what I went
through it was not unnecessary it was
not unfruitful today I stand and count
my
blessings people say
[Music]
I don't like that
song There's no way God will tender and
you can't ala I don't like it maybe it
means something else but taken from Face
Value there's no way God will tender and
you can't a Les if anything someone else
sings Count Your Blessings name them one
by
one count your blessings see what God
at
them count your
blessings name them one by
one and it will surprise you What the
Lord Has Done you can't tell me that you
cannot
teller you
can't the Church of God thrives on the
blood of the lamb and the word of his
testimony
allow me do one more thing and then we
call it an
evening just one
more God loves to hear
us give him the thanks and
praise for what he does in our lives
every day every day the word of the Lord
says from the rising of the sun till
it's setting down the name of the Lord
must be
praised and so for
me the other day I was going through my
books and I found some journals I would
keep and I said I will go back I call
them Journal of
thanks I was just arranging my bedroom
and I came across a big fire I would
write the date write the current
situation and when the day the day the
Lord answers I write the date and how it
was
answered I think it's a nice thing to do
is the only way to count your blessings
naming them one by one and for me I
don't want to forget what God is doing
in my life I
don't when the enemy
throws a trial and I'm tempted to
complain what I do is I PE one of these
journals and I read a few pages and
remind myself that I serve a God who is
able and soon I am rejoicing and
praising
God not only for what he has
done but also for what he is doing and
what he will do
Doo not only
that these channels have always said I
can pass them
down as a legacy of my faith to my
children for them to know that their
mother was a True Believer
in the
Lord that I trusted him and he heard my
prayers we must learn to thank the Lord
as we
fight the war is Raging but I can tell
you you are not broken thank the
Lord you can still afford to go to work
thank the Lord people have been
dismissed for
nonperformance because of what they're
going
through they've been referred to
counselors 3 months it's not working and
finally they're dismissed from work they
come for four you can still perform at
work thank
God children of
God there's been a drought
in your
life you want the rain so badly that you
cannot see the dark clouds
gathering so
badly I am urging you go out look toward
the sea you shall see a cloud the size
of a man's
hand that is evidence there's a sound of
an abundance of Ray soon it will rain
it's been dry but your life will BD
again because the one we serve is a
restorer is it not the Bible that says I
will restore what the locusts have eaten
is it yes swimming locusts swmming
flying crawling what all manner of
locusts have eaten in your life the Lord
says I will
restore and this is what I love about my
Lord I keep repeating certain
foundational statements that I make when
the Lord comes in to restore he
catapults you to where you ought to have
been at this point in
life so when you think your friends have
moved so far the day your restoration
comes he catapults you slightly ahead of
your
friends trust in the
Lord trust in the
Lord allow me sing this song all of us
the chist Has Come To God Be The Glory
great things is done
[Music]
to God be the glory great he done so L
he the world that he
gave his son who us his life
at
for bring our
reest that all may go in Praise the Lord
praise the Lord let the
he praise the Lord praise the Lord let
the people
rej oh come to
father through Jesus the
son and give him the glory great things
he have
done
oh perfect
Redemption the PES
of to
every the promise of God the
vess
offender who truly
believes
God from Jesus the Bon
rece praise the Lord praise the Lord let
the Earth re voice praise the Lord
praise the Lord let the people re
oh come to the father through Jesus the
son and give him the glory great things
he has
done
great let me have all my
ERS
great has done and great our rejoicing
through Jesus the
son
p and higher and greater will be our
Wonder our transport when Jesus we see
praise the Lord praise the Lord let the
Earth he re voice praise the Lord prise
the Lord let the people
rej oh come to the father through Jesus
the
son and give him the
glory great things
he
done as they are still bringing we can
sing one more song it is the Blessed
Hour of Prayer
as I have all our pastors and all our
elders
come Pastor rundu you will pray for us
is a blessed Hour of Prayer
51 I hope we not locking anyone
out 51 is a blessed pray we'll just sing
one
stanza as uh our pastors and Elders come
it's one
stanza it is the Blessed Hour of Prayer
te
blessed when
heart
Ree and we GA to
Jesus our
saor and
friend if we come to him
in his
protection to share
water B for
the oh how sweet to be
there
blessed of
PR
blessed water B
for the we
oh how sweet to be
there the spirit has just reminded me
something it would be bad if I don't say
it when we thank the
Lord
periodically learn to bring an offering
of Thanksgiving to the Lord
periodically for this sabbath we shall
be and offering of sacrifice to exchange
with the Lord but as he continues to
answer you periodically come before the
Lord with an offering of what you just
know this is for Thanksgiving no one
says thanks empty-handed is it no one no
one with the same intensity you sought
his face with the same intensity say
thank you to him let me teach you
something about fasting if you fasted
for an answer fast to thank the Lord
when it finally comes do a fast to thank
the Lord for it and complete it with a
Thanksgiving what offering as we kneel
down let us all kneel down pastor rundo
we pray for
us Ro
[Music]
oh to
she
to
Leo
Fe who to
[Music]
now go on
You by
[Music]
Our Father in
Heaven thank you for the message
today the reminder that we should
be looking towards the
sea to look at the signs of this
abundance of
rain every single day you will put a
sign on our way but we do not see that
because we want to
see the blessing and not the process of
the
blessing but you have reminded us the
process is
important and now Lord we are sorry that
we were in a rush for the
blessing in the process we get to know
the
blesser we get to trust him even more
thank you Lord for every single thing
you've done in our lives no matter how
small small thank you for
them may you build our faith to embrace
them that we might remember the small
things you have done that they will
assure us that the rain is
coming father there are people who have
brought in their requests in this box of
prayer I pray on their behalf and on my
behalf too dear Lord that you hear the
and answer us in accordance to your will
thank you because you have forgiven us
our sins for everyone who has
confessed because your word says that if
we confess our sin you are faithful and
just to forgive us of our
sins thank you because we will stand
from here knowing that you have forgiven
us and you have cleansed us from all our
unrighteousness and thank you because
that is the main and most powerful F
answer to any prayer that your sins are
forgiven now because you're forgiven our
sins any other request you have brought
before you dear Lord may you answer it
in accordance to your will
amen we thank you because the healing
that has started in somebody's
life we thank you because there's
Restoration in somebody's
family we thank you Lord
because somebody who is in depression
you're lifting up the dark cloud from
their hearts and a shine of light is
coming through their hearts thank you
because there's somebody who Lord who
has sought for your face and for a long
time there has been a veil they have
never seen your face they don't know how
your voice sounds but today you're
speaking to
them thank you because there's somebody
was giving
up but today you have given them a new
Lee of faith and their life will be
restored now we turn to you dear Lord
who is able to do exceedingly and
abundantly above what we ask or
imagine and we say like David The Lord
Is Our Shepherd and because you Lord are
Our Shepherd we sure enough know that we
shall not be in want because you will
lead us
besides then the Still Waters and you
will make us lie down in Green Pastures
you will restore our souls you will
restore our dying Souls you will restore
our souls for your righteousness sake
and yet though sometimes we walk through
the valley of the shadow of death we
shall fear no EV for thou Lord art with
us thou art with us thy Road and thy
stuff oh they confort
us thank you for preparing a table
before us even in the presence of our
enemies oh thank you for inviting us
into that
dinner and thank you for anointing our
head once more with
oil thank you dear Lord for our
[Music]
cup is running over amen surely
goodness and mercy shall follow us all
the days of our lives and we declare
this day in response to your goodness
that we shall dwell in the house in your
house
forever and ever and let everyone who
believes Say Amen
Our Father Who Art in Heaven hallowe be
thy name thy kingdom come thy will be
done on Earth as it is in heaven give us
this day our daily bread and forgive us
our trespasses as we forgive those who
trespass against us lead us not into
temptation but Deliver Us from the evil
one for thine is the kingdom the power
and the glory for for ever and ever
amen Lord Jesus Christ and the love of
God and The Fellowship of the Holy
Spirit be with us now and forever more
amen amen